Are you ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
Children: Aye, aye, Captain!
孩子们：是啊是啊，队长！
I can't hear you!
我听不到你说话！
Children: Aye, aye, Captain!
孩子们：是啊是啊，队长！
♪ Ohh... ♪
♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
队长：♪ 吸水性的，黄色的
他是多孔的 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ If nautical nonsense
be somethin' you wish ♪
船长：♪ 如果是航海方面的废话
成为你所希望的那样 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
船长：♪ 然后降落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Ready? ♪
队长：♪ 准备好了吗？ ♪
All: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
全部： ♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ SpongeBob
SquarePants ♪
队长：♪ 海绵宝宝
方裤♪
What are you doing, Mr. Krabs?
蟹老板，你在做什么？
Just making sure
the Krabby Patty formula
is safe.
只是确定
蟹黄饼配方
是安全的。
Plankton hasn't tried to steal
the formula in over a month.
浮游生物并没有试图偷窃
一个多月内的公式。
He must be planning
something big.
他一定是在计划
一些大事。
Hello.
你好。
One of you will have to
volunteer for some extra work.
你们中的一个人必须
自愿做一些额外的工作。
Goodbye.
再见。
I was just gonna ask if someone
could spy on Plankton.
我只是想问是否有人
可以监视浮游生物。
Spy?
间谍？
Ooh!
哦！
Hey, SpongeBob, I can see you
through this straw.
嘿，海绵宝宝，我能看到你
通过这根稻草。
Patrick, I'm gonna be a spy!
帕特里克，我要成为一名间谍！
You're a spy?
你是间谍？
I want to be a spy, too!
我也想当间谍！
Shh, OK, OK.
嘘，好吧，好吧。
You can be a spy.
你可以成为一名间谍。
Just be quiet.
安静点。
Hooray!
万岁！
We're spy buddies!
我们是间谍伙伴！
Shh.
嘘。
: Spy buddies.
: 间谍伙伴。
Your instructions are on
this Krabby Patty, but remember
您的指示已开启
这个蟹肉饼，但记住
the fate of the Krusty Krab
rests in your hands, SpongeBob.
蟹堡王的命运
一切都在你的手中，海绵宝宝。
In my hands.
在我手中。
Ooh.
哦。
Krabs: Your mission,
if you choose to accept it
蟹蟹：你的使命，
如果你选择接受
is to discover
what Plankton's up to.
是去发现
浮游生物在做什么。
Don't let him out of your sight.
别让他离开你的视线。
You'll need to rustle up
some spy gadgets.
你需要振作起来
一些间谍小工具。
If you don't accept it,
you're fired.
如果你不接受的话
你被解雇了。
This patty will self-destruct
in 10 seconds.
这个肉饼会自毁
10 秒后。
Get rid of it.
摆脱它。
Get rid of it, Patrick.
摆脱它，帕特里克。
That's gonna leave a mark.
那会留下痕迹的
Hi, Sandy.
嗨，桑迪。
Hey, SpongeBob, Patrick.
嘿，海绵宝宝，帕特里克。
What y'all doin'?
你们都在做什么？
Do you know anything about
spying, Sandy?
你知道什么吗
间谍，桑迪？
Well, I know you need
a lot of crazy gadgets,
like jet packs
嗯，我知道你需要
很多疯狂的小玩意，
像喷气背包
and laser-equipped
Bermuda shorts
with walkie-talkies.
并配备激光
百慕大短裤
与对讲机。
Man: 10-4, good buddy.
男：10-4，好哥们。
Cameras that fit
up your nose, high-powered
magnifying glasses...
适合的相机
抬起你的鼻子，高能
放大镜...
And my favorite,
the knockout ray.
还有我最喜欢的，
淘汰射线。
Wow, Sandy.
哇，桑迪。
With these gadgets, Patrick
and I will be great spies.
有了这些小玩意，帕特里克
我会成为伟大的间谍。
I wouldn't trust you two
with any of this stuff.
我不会相信你们两个
与任何这些东西。
What do we do now, Patrick?
我们现在该怎么办，帕特里克？
What's he doing now?
他现在在做什么？
Nothing yet.
还什么都没有。
Wait, wait, he's...
等等，等等，他...
buying baby clothes?
买婴儿衣服？
We got to get closer.
我们必须靠近一点。
Excuse me.
打扰一下。
Do you have anything
in a size negative five?
你有什么吗
尺寸为负五？
Uh, sorry, bud.
呃，抱歉，伙计。
That's as small as they come.
这和他们来的一样小。
Wow, Plankton has to
buy baby clothes?
哇，浮游生物必须
买婴儿衣服吗？
How embarrassing.
多么尴尬啊。
SpongeBob to Krabs.
从海绵宝宝到蟹蟹。
Come in, Krabs.
进来吧，蟹蟹。
Krabs here.
这里有螃蟹。
Go ahead.
前进。
Plankton just bought
some baby clothes.
刚买的浮游生物
一些婴儿衣服。
Baby clothes?
婴儿衣服？
Hm.
嗯。
What's he doing now?
他现在在做什么？
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
He's buying...
他要买...
Yeah, yeah?
是啊是啊？
A stamp.
一张邮票。
This is the most
elaborate scheme ever.
这是最
精心设计的计划。
Keep on him, SpongeBob.
继续追随他，海绵宝宝。
We're right behind him,
and he has no idea.
我们就在他身后
他不知道。
Would you stop making
all that racket?
你能停止做吗
那些喧闹？
What's he doing now?
他现在在做什么？
I can't tell.
我不知道。
Phew, gosh, it's hot.
唷，天哪，好热。
He's getting away.
他要离开了。
Quick, Patrick,
use the jet pack.
快点，帕特里克，
使用喷气背包。
Can do.
可以做。
Phew.
唷。
Huh?
啊？
Boy, it was lucky
the sidewalk broke our fall.
男孩，真幸运
人行道阻止了我们的跌倒。
But we lost Plankton.
但我们失去了浮游生物。
To the spy-mobile.
到间谍车。
Hm.
嗯。
Mines, oil slick,
smoke screen, shield.
矿山、浮油、
烟幕，盾牌。
Patrick: Self-destruct.
帕特里克：自毁。
There's a call coming through
on my "pants-o-phone."
有电话打过来
在我的“裤子手机”上。
Krabs: Krabs to agent SpongeBob.
蟹老板：蟹老板对海绵宝宝特工。
Come in, SpongeBob.
进来吧，海绵宝宝。
It's for you.
这是给你的。
Agent SpongeBob here.
海绵宝宝特工在这里。
Krabs: Have you found out
what Plankton's up to?
蟹蟹：你发现了吗？
浮游生物在做什么？
I'm afraid
we lost him, Mr. Krabs.
我害怕
我们失去了他，蟹老板。
Well, find him, lad.
好吧，找到他，小伙子。
I'm not paying you
to goof off with Patrick.
我不付钱给你
和帕特里克偷懒。
You're not paying me
at all, Mr. Krabs.
你不付钱给我
无论如何，蟹老板。
Exactly, so get to work!
没错，所以开始工作吧！
Operator: If you'd like to make
a call, please deposit 25 cents.
接线员：如果您愿意的话
打电话，请存25美分。
SpongeBob: OK, Patrick,
we're in position.
海绵宝宝：好的，帕特里克，
我们已就位。
Now, how do we get inside?
现在，我们如何进去？
I think the front door's open.
我认为前门是开着的。
Spies don't use
the front door, Patrick.
间谍不使用
前门，帕特里克。
We've got to figure out
a complicated way to get inside.
我们必须弄清楚
进入内部的方法很复杂。
This looks like a job
for Patrick star laser pants.
这看起来像是一份工作
帕特里克星激光裤。
Ooh.
哦。
Good work, Patrick.
干得好，帕特里克。
Now, it's my turn.
现在，轮到我了。
I thought you were holding
the rope.
我以为你拿着
绳子。
I am.
我是。
You need to be quiet.
你需要保持安静。
We're on a secret mission.
我们正在执行一项秘密任务。
Plankton: Secret mission, Eh?
浮游生物：秘密任务，嗯？
Don't you think
I know what you're up to?
你不觉得
我知道你在做什么？
You want to eat at
the Chum Bucket without
your boss knowing.
你想吃在
没有的密友桶
你的老板知道。
Karen, we've got a customer.
凯伦，我们有一位顾客。
I'll let you two
look over the menu.
我让你们两个
查看菜单。
SpongeBob, I have to go.
海绵宝宝，我得走了。
Oh, can't you go later?
哦，你不能晚点走吗？
My laser pants
aren't working right.
我的激光裤
工作不正常。
Can I interest you in
a raspberry iced tea?
我可以让你感兴趣吗
覆盆子冰茶？
No, thanks.
不，谢谢。
Or perhaps a bran muffin?
或者也许是麸皮松饼？
SpongeBob, I have to go now.
海绵宝宝，我得走了。
Prune Danish?
修剪丹麦语？
What the...?
什么……？
Destroy my lab, will you, Krabs?
毁掉我的实验室，好吗，蟹蟹？
Well, if it's war you want,
it's war you'll get!
好吧，如果你想要战争，
你会得到战争！
Is it dark, or have I put off
my cataract surgery too long?
天黑了吗，还是我推迟了
我的白内障手术时间太长了吗？
No, Mr. Krabs,
it's that time of the month.
不，蟹老板先生，
现在是每个月的这个时候。
Krabs: Merciful Neptune!
蟹蟹：仁慈的海王星！
Man your battle stations.
管理你的战斗站。
I'm on it.
我正在做。
Bring it on, Plankton.
加油吧，浮游生物。
Plankton: Oh, I will.
浮游生物：哦，我会的。
We'll see if you have
a customer left after
I pump up the volume.
我们会看看你是否有
一位顾客离开后
我把音量调大。
Oh, brother.
哦，兄弟。
I hated the real version
of this song.
我讨厌真实版本
这首歌的。
He's driving me customers away.
他正在赶走我的顾客。
All right, Plankton,
you want my customers so badly?
好吧，浮游生物，
你这么想要我的顾客吗？
You can have 'em.
你可以拥有它们。
Do your worst, Krabs!
蟹蟹们，尽你所能吧！
I hate my job.
我讨厌我的工作。
It's up to you and me, buddy.
这取决于你和我，伙计。
Abandon ship.
弃船。
Pointy-headed projectile
on the port side.
尖头弹丸
在左舷。
No!
不！
I win!
我赢了！
I always win!
我总是赢！
Not to rain on
your parade or anything,
but you always lose.
不让下雨
你的游行或者其他什么，
但你总是会输。
No, SpongeBob, I always win.
不，海绵宝宝，我总是赢。
Mr. Krabs?
蟹老板？
That's right.
这是正确的。
I stole me own formula.
我偷了我自己的配方。
But if you're Mr. Krabs,
then who's...?
但如果你是蟹老板
那么谁是...？
SpongeBob: Mr. Krabs is a robot!
海绵宝宝：蟹老板是一个机器人！
No, you idiot.
不，你这个白痴。
SpongeBob: Plankton?
海绵宝宝：浮游生物？
What the barnacles
is going on here?
什么是藤壶
这是怎么回事？
You see, we had a bet.
你看，我们打赌了。
Plankton's been trying
for 20 years
浮游生物一直在努力
20年来
to steal the formula,
and he's never done it.
窃取公式，
但他从来没有这样做过。
I almost had it 37 times,
and you know it.
我差点就经历了37次
你知道的。
Tell it to the claw, sister.
告诉爪子吧，姐姐。
Last time he failed,
we made a bet.
上次他失败了，
我们打赌。
You can't beat me, Plankton.
你打不过我，浮游生物。
I always win.
我总是赢。
You've got the easy part.
你已经完成了简单的部分。
I'd like to see you do  my  job.
我希望看到你完成我的工作。
Oh, yeah, right.
哦，是的，没错。
If I was you, I could steal
the formula on me first try.
如果我是你，我就可以偷东西
我先尝试一下公式。
Hah!
哈！
The usual wager?
平常的赌注？
You're on.
你开始了。
So, through a series of events
far too elaborate
to go into right now
于是，通过一系列的事件
过于复杂
现在就进入
we flawlessly assumed
each other's lives
我们完美地假设
彼此的生活
and I beat Plankton
at his own game, and destroyed
his place of business.
我打败了浮游生物
在他自己的游戏中，并摧毁了
他的营业地点。
Now pay up.
现在付钱吧。
Here you go, Eugene.
给你，尤金。
One dollar.
一美元。
Not so fast.
没那么快。
Squidward?
章鱼哥？
Then who are you?
那你是谁？
I'm not...
我不是...
...wearing a disguise.
……乔装打扮。
Hm, if he's Squidward,
then you must be... Sandy?
嗯，如果他是章鱼哥，
那你一定是……桑迪？
Whoops, wrong outfit.
哎呀，穿错衣服了。
You're me.
你就是我。
Then I must be...
那我一定是...
Patrick!
帕特里克！
Nah, I'm just kidding.
不，我只是开玩笑。
I really am Patrick.
我真的是帕特里克。
Good one, Patrick.
好一个，帕特里克。
There's just one thing
I don't understand.
只有一件事
我不明白。
What's that, laddie?
那是什么，小伙子？
That.
那。
Man: Boat smarts,
with Mrs. Puff.
男人：船聪明，
和普芙夫人。
This driving safety film
is brought to you
by "COBBUTKSBSPOTRAOOBAT"
这部行车安全片
给你带来了
通过“COBBUTKSBSPOTRAOOBAT”
citizens of Bikini Bottom united
to keep SpongeBob SquarePants
比基尼泳滩的公民团结起来
保留海绵宝宝
off the road and out
of boats all together.
离开道路并出去
的船都在一起。
Good day, future motorists.
美好的一天，未来的驾车者。
I'm Mrs. Puff, state accredited
driving instructor.
我是帕夫夫人，获得国家认可
驾驶教练。
Today, we'll be discussing
the differences between
a driver with boat smarts...
今天我们要讨论的是
之间的差异
一个有船智慧的司机......
Ripping good day for
a spot of driving.
撕裂美好的一天
一个开车的地方。
...and a driver
without boat smarts.
...还有一名司机
没有船的智慧。
Hey, Squidward, look what
I can do with my feet!
嘿，章鱼哥，看什么
我用脚也能做到！
Let's see some examples,
shall we?
让我们看一些例子，
我们可以吗？
Tire pressure.
轮胎压力。
Before you can even think
about boating
在你能思考之前
关于划船
the boater who uses boat smarts
always fills his tires
to the appropriate level
使用船舶智能的划船者
总是给他的轮胎加油
到适当的水平
while this driver pays
no heed to boat smarts.
当这位司机付钱时
不关心船的智慧。
Mrs. Puff: Buckling up.
普夫夫人：系好安全带。
As demonstrated by this driver,
he has enough boat smarts
to use his seatbelt
正如这位司机所证明的那样，
他有足够的船智慧
使用安全带
and avoid a serious casualty
as a result of a collision.
并避免严重伤亡
由于碰撞。
Notice how he comes gently
to a stop sign.
注意他是如何温柔地过来的
到停车标志。
Now, this driver
with no regard for safety...
现在这位司机
不顾安全...
Mrs. Puff: Well, at least he had
his seat belt on.
普夫夫人：嗯，至少他有
他系好安全带。
Mrs. Puff: Adjusting
your mirrors.
泡芙夫人：调整中
你的镜子。
What's our boat smarts
boater up to now?
我们的船有什么智能
划船到现在？
You guessed it.
你猜对了。
He's adjusting his mirror
before he begins boating,
unlike this degenerate boater.
他正在调整镜子
在他开始划船之前，
不像这个堕落的船夫。
Ah, perfect.
啊，完美。
Hey, use your mirrors, fool.
嘿，用你的镜子，傻瓜。
Mirrors?
镜子？
Oh, that reminds me.
哦，这让我想起了。
I haven't adjusted this one yet.
这个我还没有调整过。
Ah, can't see.
啊，看不到。
Oh!
哦！
Ow.
噢。
Finally, and most importantly,
a driver with boat smarts
最后，也是最重要的一点是，
有船智慧的司机
always pays attention
to his surroundings,
and avoids distractions.
总是关注
对他的周围环境，
并避免分心。
Notice how this driver's eyes
are locked firmly on the road.
注意这位司机的眼睛
被牢牢锁在路上。
And here we have the epitome
of a driver
这里我们有一个缩影
一个司机的
who is carelessly
distracting himself from
the road and safety.
谁不小心
分散自己的注意力
道路和安全。
Jerk!
混蛋！
Hi there!
你好呀！
Help, lunatic driver!
救命啊，疯狂的司机！
How's it going?
怎么样了？
Mrs. Puff: SpongeBob, I mean,
a boater without boat smarts
泡芙夫人：海绵宝宝，我是说，
没有划船智慧的划船者
shows contempt for
his boater brethren and the law.
表示蔑视
他的船夫兄弟和法律。
SpongeBob: ♪ La, la-la-la-la,
la-la-la-la ♪
海绵宝宝：♪ 啦啦啦啦啦，
啦啦啦啦♪
Whee!
哎哟！
Hi, Squidward.
嗨，章鱼哥。
Hi, Mrs. Puff.
嗨，普芙女士。
Looks like you guys
forgot your boat smarts.
看起来像你们
忘记了你的船智慧。
Mrs. Puff: Never mind.
普芙夫人：没关系。
Exciting meeting, Mr. Krabs?
令人兴奋的会面吗，蟹老板？
Oh, you bet you, SpongeBob.
噢，你敢打赌，海绵宝宝。
Listen to this.
听听这个。
Individuation of the end user
will substantially broaden
最终用户的个性化
将大幅拓宽
the probability of multiple
subsequent visits
多重的概率
随后的访问
generating an inverse
negative revenue margin
生成逆
负收入利润率
of 3/4 of
1/2 of one percent.
的 3/4
百分之一的 1/2。
Meaning, if you call
the customers by their name
意思是，如果你打电话
顾客的名字
they keep coming back to spend
more of their greenbacks
他们不断回来消费
更多的美元
so I want you two to learn
the names of every customer.
所以我想让你们两个学习
每个顾客的名字。
I have an important life
to live, and it doesn't include
chattering with you two ninnies.
我有重要的人生
生活，它不包括
和你们两个傻瓜聊天。
I thought you might say that,
so I decided to turn this
into a contest.
我以为你可能会这么说
所以我决定改变这个
参加比赛。
The employee who learns
more names wins this.
学习的员工
更多的名字会赢得胜利。
A tropical getaway,
on the triple-decker Con-Huge-Co
cruise liner.
热带度假胜地，
在三层甲板 Con-Huge-Co 上
游轮。
Sunbathing, Parcheesi,
ballroom dancing.
日光浴，帕奇西，
交际舞。
This is gonna be so easy.
这会很容易。
SpongeBob doesn't realize that
I'm the face of the Krusty Krab.
海绵宝宝并没有意识到这一点
我是蟹堡王的代言人。
While he's isolated
in the kitchen all day
当他被孤立时
整天在厨房里
I've been out here, building
a rapport with the customer.
我一直在这里，建造
与客户的融洽关系。
Hello.
你好。
May I get you
anything else, miss?
我可以得到你吗
还有什么吗，小姐？
Since when do you give
two shrimps about
customer service
从什么时候开始你给
两只虾大约
客户服务
Mister Grouchy Squid Guy?
脾气暴躁的乌贼男先生？
SpongeBob: Hi, Sally.
海绵宝宝：嗨，莎莉。
Hi, Sadie.
嗨，萨迪。
Hi, Shoobie.
嗨，舒比。
How does SpongeBob
know all these names?
海绵宝宝是怎样做的
知道所有这些名字吗？
Right back at you, Lenny.
就在你身边，莱尼。
Hey, SpongeBob, could you take
a look at the cash register?
嘿，海绵宝宝，你能接受吗
看一下收银机？
I think it's broken.
我认为它坏了。
Oh, sure, Squidward.
哦，当然，章鱼哥。
I think you might need
a closer look.
我想你可能需要
仔细看看。
Let me give you a hand.
让我帮你。
I can't see anything
in here, Squidward.
我什么也看不见
在这里，章鱼哥。
Keep looking, SpongeBob.
继续寻找，海绵宝宝。
Keep on looking.
继续寻找。
So, what's your name?
那么，你叫什么名字？
Hi, Thaddeus.
嗨，撒迪厄斯。
Goodbye, SpongeBob.
再见，海绵宝宝。
That should buy me enough time
to win that cruise.
这应该能为我赢得足够的时间
赢得那次巡航。
Good day, young sir.
美好的一天，年轻的先生。
My name is...
我的名字是...
Gus!
格斯！
He's right.
他是对的。
This guy's so good,
you should give him a prize.
这人真好
你应该给他一个奖品。
How in Neptune's creation
do you know all of
these names, SpongeBob?
海王星是如何创造的
你知道全部吗
这些名字，海绵宝宝？
Well, I simply compile the name
of every customer in this book.
好吧，我简单编一下名字
本书中的每一位客户。
Thanks, SpongeBob.
谢谢，海绵宝宝。
Let's see.
让我们来看看。
Halpert, Norma, Isabelle, Gus,
Chaz, Pilar, Dennis, Kira,
Ivy, Marv, Mable, Mavis.
哈尔珀特、诺玛、伊莎贝尔、格斯、
查兹、皮拉尔、丹尼斯、基拉、
艾薇、马夫、梅布尔、梅维斯。
And your name
is Suzy Fish, correct?
还有你的名字
苏西·菲什是吗？
Yes, and you'd also be correct
in saying you ruined my food
with your sweat, you nitwit!
是的，你也是对的
说你毁了我的食物
用你的汗水，你这个白痴！
Mr. Krabs,
that's the last customer.
蟹老板先生，
那是最后一位顾客。
Do I win?
我赢了吗？
Uh, well, actually,
I wasn't keeping score.
呃，实际上，
我没有记分。
But I'll just say that you
and SpongeBob are neck and neck
但我只想说你
和海绵宝宝不分上下
and that mystery guy
over there'll be the tiebreaker.
还有那个神秘人
那边将进行决胜局。
Uh, that's, uh...
呃，那个，呃……
Oh, that's, I know him.
哦，原来如此，我认识他。
He's the ticket to your prize.
他是你获得奖品的门票。
Out of the way, loser.
走开，失败者。
Um, hello.
嗯，你好。
My name is Squidward.
我的名字是章鱼哥。
Uh, so, what's your name?
呃，那么，你叫什么名字？
What's it to you?
关你什么事？
Um, it's just that I was going
to, um, enter your name
in our sweepstakes.
嗯，只是我要去
嗯，输入你的名字
在我们的抽奖活动中。
So, what should I put down?
那么，我应该放下什么呢？
First and last name?
名字和姓氏？
Sure.
当然。
Yeah, why don't you
write this on your form.
是的，你为什么不
将其写在您的表格上。
What's it to you!
关你什么事！
Now leave me alone.
现在别管我了。
I see he wants
to play hard to get.
我看他想要
玩得来之不易。
So be it.
就这样吧。
I have ways of making
the likes of him talk.
我有办法制作
像他这样的人会说话。
Uh, sir, you forgot your soda.
呃，先生，你忘记带苏打水了。
I didn't order any soda.
我没有点苏打水。
It's on the house.
就在房子上。
What the barnacles
are you doing?
什么是藤壶
你在做什么？
Oh, I'm sorry, I slipped.
哦，对不起，我滑倒了。
Here, let me clean
that up for you.
来，让我打扫一下
这就是为你准备的。
OK, there must be a nametag
or some form of I.D. in here.
好的，必须有名牌
或某种形式的身份证件在这里。
I don't need your help.
我不需要你的帮助。
I'm out of here.
我要离开这里了
Hey, look up in the sky.
嘿，抬头看看天空。
A giant meteor
is hurtling towards Earth.
一颗巨大的流星
正在冲向地球。
Where?
在哪里？
Oh, you'll see it.
哦，你会看到的。
Just keep looking.
继续寻找吧。
I can't see it.
我看不到它。
Well, that's too bad, 'cause
I found what I was looking for.
嗯，那太糟糕了，因为
我找到了我要找的东西。
Hey, come back here!
嘿，回来吧！
Give me my wallet!
把我的钱包给我！
Holy sea cow!
圣海牛！
That hooligan ran a stop sign.
那个流氓闯了停车标志。
Stop, thief!
站住，小偷！
You know that guy?
你认识那个人吗？
Hardly.
几乎没有。
He stole my wallet.
他偷了我的钱包。
What?
什么？
That makes him a dual offender.
这使他成为双重犯罪者。
Let's get him.
我们来抓住他吧。
Finally, the moment of truth.
最后，关键时刻。
Say goodbye
to anonymity, mister...
说再见
匿名，先生...
Freeze, thief!
冻结，小偷！
No, you don't understand.
不，你不明白。
I only want the wallet for...
我只想要钱包...
We know exactly why
you want it, wallet snatcher.
我们确切地知道原因
你想要它，抢钱包的人。
This isn't as it seems!
这并不像看上去的那样！
That's what you'll be saying
in the slammer, punk.
这就是你会说的
在猛击者中，朋克。
His driver's license.
他的驾驶执照。
At last, at last!
终于，终于！
And your name is...
而你的名字是...
Mr. "What Zit Tooya?"
“什么Zit Tooya？”先生。
What kind of ridiculous
name is that?
哪有什么可笑的
名字是那个？
It's my ridiculous name.
这是我可笑的名字。
"What Zit Tooya."
“什么Zit Tooya。”
That's enough of that ballyhoo.
那些大肆宣传就够了。
But I didn't intentionally
do anything wrong.
但我不是故意的
做任何错事。
Tell it to the judge,
law breaker.
告诉法官，
违法者。
Only 364 days
and nine years left
只有364天
还剩九年
until I exchange
this concrete tomb for a
multi-story ocean liner cruise.
直到我交换
这座混凝土坟墓
多层远洋客轮巡航。
SpongeBob: Hey, Squidward.
海绵宝宝：嘿，章鱼哥。
Squidward: SpongeBob.
章鱼哥：海绵宝宝。
The boy and I just thought
we'd stop by and check on
our convict friend.
我和男孩只是想
我们会过来看看
我们的囚犯朋友。
Call me what you may.
你可以怎么称呼我。
Fact of the matter is,
I found out the mystery
customer's name first, so I win.
事情的真相是，
我发现了其中的奥秘
客户的名字在前，所以我赢了。
I win, I win, I win,
I win, I win.
我赢了我赢了我赢了
我赢了，我赢了。
Enjoy your prize.
享受你的奖品吧。
Whoo-hoo!
呼呼！
Tropical vacation, here I come!
热带度假，我来了！
Vacation?
假期？
Who said anything
about vacation?
谁说了什么
关于假期？
What?
什么？
In the brochure,
it specifically mentions
an ocean liner vacation.
在宣传册中，
它特别提到
远洋客轮假期
Oh, you mean  that  brochure?
哦，你是说那本小册子吗？
Well, that was the prize.
嗯，这就是奖品。
The brochure was taking up
too much room in me drawers,
you know, so it's your prize.
宣传册已被占用
我抽屉里的空间太多了
你知道，所以这是你的奖品。
You mean, no vacation.
你的意思是，没有假期。
Nope, just the brochure.
不，只是小册子。
Well, got to get back
to counting me loot.
嗯，得回去了
来数我的战利品。
Enjoy your new prize, Squidward.
享受你的新奖品吧，章鱼哥。
See you on the outside
in 10 years, buddy.
在外面见
10年后，伙计。
Oh, well.
那好吧。
At least I'll have some peace
and quiet for the next 10 years.
至少我会得到一些平静
并在接下来的10年里保持安静。
Patrick: Hey, Squidward.
帕特里克：嘿，章鱼哥。
Parcheesi?
帕奇西？